# **Teerapong Nokaew**

### Full Stack Developer

Full-Stack Developer with over 1 year of experience in building web applications using PHP, Laravel, Node.js, and MySQL. Skilled in both frontend and backend development with a focus on clean, user-friendly design. Enjoy learning new technologies and improving skills continuously.

#### **Work Experience**

# Computer Officer | Multidisciplinary Research Institute - Chiang Mai University

Jul 2024 - Present

- Develop and maintain the organization's website to ensure optimal performance. (www.mdri.cmu.ac.th)
- Design, develop, and implement internal web applications to improve business operations.
- Collaborate with other teams to gather requirements and develop solutions that improve efficiency.

### Full Stack Developer | Freelance

Jan 2024 - Jun 2024

- Developed a modern and professional corporate website to enhance the organization's online presence.
- Built a responsive web-based food ordering system to ensure smooth user experience across all devices.
- Created an E-Commerce website with a full-featured product and order management system.

### WordPress Developer (Intern) | Greyscale Digital co. Itd

Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

- Build and design website pages using WordPress and Elementor based on design.
- Customize themes and templates for design and functionality.
- Ensure responsive design for optimal user experience across all devices.
- Work with the design team to integrate visual elements seamlessly.

### **Educational Background**

# Rajamangala University of Technology Lanna Bachelor's Degree

Business Information System - Software Development in Business Jun 2021 - Mar 2024

GPA: 3.81

# PAYAP Technological and Business College High Vocational Certificate

Business Administration, Information Technology May 2019 - Mar 2021 GPA: 3.94 (First Class Honors)

## PAYAP Technological and Business College Vocational Certificate

Business Administration, Information Technology May 2016 - Mar 2019 GPA: 3.52 Contact

172 Paphai Sansai Chiang Mai 50210 teerapong.nokaew07@gmail.com 095-5479821

Portfolio: www.teerapongdev.com

#### **Skills**

#### **Programming Language**

- HTML, CSS
- PHP
- JavaScript
- MySQL

### Framework & Library

- Laravel
- Node.js (Express.js)
- Jquery
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS

#### **Tools**

- Git
- Docker
- · Adobe XD, Figma

### Language

- Thai (Native)
- English

### **Projects**

#### **SROI - CMU**

- Developed a web-based system to support researchers in calculating and reporting the social value generated by projects.
- Using PHP (MVC architecture) and MySQL for Database

### Community Issue Reporting System via LINE OA

 Developed the backend using Node.js and Express.js, integrating with LINE API to receive and manage issue reports